indiafascinates.com 2015-06-22

# Privacy Policy | India Fascinates

This is the website of India Fascinates.

## Privacy Policy at India Fascinates

Any personal information you provide to us like name, e-mail address, address and telephone number will not be released, sold or rented to any entities or individuals outside of India Fascinates.

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates.

## Credit card and Financial details

India Fascinates will never ask for Credit Card details and request you _NOT_ to share it through any of the forms on India Fascinates.

## External Sites

India Fascinates is not responsible for the content of external sites linked from pages on this site. You are advised to read the privacy policy of such external sites before disclosing any personal information or entering into any transaction on such sites.

## With respect to Cookies and Advertisers

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows India Fascinates to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and India Fascinates does not use cookies to collect personal information. Our site and third parties such as advertisers may add a cookie to help analyze web traffic or to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences. 

We allow third-party advertising companies (like [Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense/)) to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These third party ad vendors, may be placing and reading cookies on your users’ browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving on our website. Google’s use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Please note that these companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Here are some [third-party vendors](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) serving ads on this site and you may visit those vendor websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor offers this capability).

## Visitor Tracking

India Fascinates makes use of analytical software such as “Google Analytics” for statistical purposes.We at India Fascinates use this information for statistical purpose only and do not share it with any third party.

India Fascinates also makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes information such as internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time-stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks. These information are collected administer the site and ensure security, to analyze trends, track user’s movement around the site and gather demographic information. 

## Policy on User Comments

India Fascinates allows users to comment on the site. However we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion. While commenting on India Fascinates, please refrain from using content that is not suitable for ALL types of audiences.

## With respect to security

We do our best to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit on the internet and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, external sites or services accessible through India Fascinates have their own privacy policy and Terms of use.You may have to use their products or services at your own discretion.You may do well to read their policies and Terms and We may not assume responsibility for any of your actions or dealing with such third party sites.

Please contact them directly, if you have any questions on their privacy policies.

For any other information please [contact us](http://indiafascinates.com/contact/)
